Finding Aid for the Father James Harold Flye Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series 4 - Materials Related to James Agee
  - Typescript of a letter from Randall Jarrell, 30 March, 1954, and a Newsletter from The Liberal Party of New York (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Documentary about James Agee
    - “Agee”, a film by Ross Spears (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - “Agee”; correspondence re: the film (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Reviews
    - Reviews of books about James Agee (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Reviews of books written by James Agee (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Talks
    - Notes and texts by Father Flye (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - “A Remembrance of James Agee”, by Father Flye (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Writings by James Agee
    - “A Mother’s Tale”,reprint, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - History exam, St. Andrew’s, 18 May, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Letter from James Agee in response to a review of “Let Us Now Praise Famous Men” (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - List of Agee’s works (incomplete) (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous prose and poetry, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - “Now As Awareness”, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Typescripts of Agee’s poems, collected by Robert Fitzgerald (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Series 5 - Ecclesiastical Matters
  - All Saints Church, Winter Park, Florida (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Benedictines, 1958, 1961, 1965, 1973-74, 1978, n.d (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Caroline Church of Seatauket, Long Island (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, NYC, 1959-60, 1967, 1973, 1976, n.d (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Church of the Ascension and St. Agnes, Washington, D.C. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Church of the Heavenly Rest, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Church of the Resurrection, NYC, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, c, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Community of the Holy Spirit, 1956, 1958-61, n.d (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Bishop Beatty re: conduct of services at St. Andrew’s Chapel (controversy) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Diocese of Nassau and the Bahamas (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Diocese of New York, 1967, 1976-77, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Epiphany Mission, Sherwood, TN, 1956-60, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - First Congregational Church, Winter Park, FL (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Grace and St. Paul’s Lutheran Church, NYC (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Greyfriars, “The Little Chronicle”, 1924-29, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - “Holy Cross Magazine” and “News”, 1943, 1945, 1959-60, 1962, 1964-65, 1968, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Holy Cross Tracts, 1915-16, n.d (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Liturgy, 1953, 1955, 1959, 1967-73, n.d (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Liturgy (continued) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Meditations, Father Wright, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellany (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Miscellany (continued) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Miscellany (continued) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Notes (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Notes (continued) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Notes (continued) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bible story outlines---Esther, Joseph, Daniel, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Biographical (other people), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Church history, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sermons (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sermons (continued) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sermons---Requiem Eucharist (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sermons---St. Andrew’s, c, 1915-1940s (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Ordination, baptisms, certificates, 1915, 1923, 1951, 1964, n.d (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ordination of women, 1972, 1976-77, n.d. (includes personal statement by Father Flye) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, Radio and Television Division (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Publications, miscellaneous (A-D) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Publications, miscellaneous (E-N) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Publications, miscellaneous (P-W) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Sacraments, 1951, n.d (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - St. Barnabas Church, Omaha, NE, 1949, 1958-59, 1960-64, 1966-75, n.d (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - St. Barnabas Church (continued) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - St. Clement’s Church, NYC (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - St. George’s Church, NYC, 1916,1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - St. George’s Church, Wichita, KS, 1955-58 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - St. Ignatius Church NYC, 1980, n.d (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - St. James Church, Wichita, KS, 1956, 1958-60 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - St. John’s Church, Bedford, VA, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - St. John’s in the Village, NYC, 1968, 1973-74 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - St. Luke’s Church, NYC, 1954, 1959-62, 1966, 1971-80, n.d (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - St. Luke’s Church, NYC (continued) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - St. Luke’s Church, NYC (continued) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - St. Mark’s in the Bouwerie, NYC (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - St. Mary’s Church, NYC, 1960-62 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - St. Paul’s Parish, Washington, D.C., 1959-61, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sisters of the Sorrowful Mother, Milwaukee, WI, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Sisters of the Tabernacle---“The Associate”, 1925, 1927-28 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - “Spiritual Mobilization” (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tracts and Pamphlets, 1905, 1941, 1956, 1966, n.d (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Trappists (Cistercians), Conyers, GA, 1948-49 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Trappists, Berryville, VA, 1975, n.d (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Trappists---Correspondence, 1952-52, 1957-58 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Trappists---General, 1946,1952,n.d (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Trappists, Gethsemani, KY, correspondence, 1919-20, 1935, 1938, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Trappists---General, 1952, n.d (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Trappists---pictures (postcards, no messages) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Trinity Church, NYC (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - University of the South, Sewanee, TN, 1938, 1952, 1959, 1969, n.d (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Series 6 - St. Andrew’s School
  - Alumni News, 1969-70, 1976, n.d (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1976-80 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1950s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Crest, 1960-81 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - EQB Club---Father Flye’s notes of meetings, c, 1933-36 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lettermen’s initiation (hazing); notes and correspondence (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Letters, announcements, memoranda, 1930s-1960s, n.d (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Literary publications, 1926, 1980, n.d (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Maroon and White and Maroon Tribune, 1939-40, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Messenger and other fund-raising appeals, 1933-82 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellany (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mountain Lion, 1931, 1940-43, 1945, n.d (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - News releases, 1980, n.d (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1976,1978-80, n.d (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1950, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Roll call, 1918-1919, 1920s, 1940-41, n.d (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Student regulations, 1930s, n.d (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Student work (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Student work, 1919 (continued) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student work, 1920s (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (continued) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (continued) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (continued) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (continued) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Student work, 1930s-1950s (continued) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Grade reports, 1943, n.d (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Gradebooks
    - September 1919-May 1921 and September 1926-May 1929 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - September 1929-May 1932 and September 1932-May 1934 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - September 1934-May 1936 and September 1936-May 1938 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - September 1938-May 1940 and September 1941-May 1944 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - September 1944-May 1946 and September 1946-September 1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - September 1949-May 1951 and September 1951-May 1953 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - September 1953-May 1954 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Yearbooks
    Nine yearbooks for the years 1926, 1947, 1948, 1952, 1955, 1964, 1970, 1972 (2 copies)
  - Memorabilia
    - National Association of Independent Schools---Annual Book Award ---“Presented to James Agee, March, 1963 for The Letters of James Agee to Father Flye” (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Birthday card made and signed by St. Andrew’s students
      - St. Andrew’s Certificate of Appreciation and St. Andrew’s Medallion
      - Guest register for Father Flye---Alumni Weekend, 1976 [caution: sharp edge on pen holder]
      - National Honor Society (Alpha Beta Kappa) honorary membership---charm and certificate
      - French word list
      - Spencerian Penmanship, n.d
- Series 7 - Education
  - Class Lecture Notes
    - Botany (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Botany (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Economics (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - English (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - English (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - English (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - English (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - English (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - History (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - History (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - History (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - History (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - History (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Latin (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Math (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Math (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Natural History (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Natural History (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Psychology (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Religion/Theology (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Religion/Theology (last file of class lecture notes) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Exams---rhetoric, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Paper---“The Psalms as Vehicles of Christian Worship” n.d. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Entrance exam for Yale (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Yale Review (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Miscellany (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Nomination for Honorary Degree (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - University of Virginia---Record of Commencement (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Education - Bulletins - Rollins College, 1915 - 1917, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Education - Bulletins - Yale, 1906 -1909, 1935-36 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Education - Bulletins - University of Virginia, 1911 - 1912, 1913 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Education - Bulletins - General Theological Seminary, 1914, 1962, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    The Yale Banner and Potpourri, 1909 - 1910
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. I (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. I, 1st supplement (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. I, 2nd supplement (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. II (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. III (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. IV (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. V (Box 27)
  - History of the Class of 1910 Yale College: Vol. VI (Box 27)
  - Class books for 1940, 1946, 1955 (2), 1970 (2) (Box 27)
- Series 8 - Notes, Miscellaneous
  - Atlantic Monthly, index (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Chambers, Whittaker---notes from a conversation with, September 25, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Copied material and miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Costa, Robert--- typescripts of conversations---1969-70, c, 1983, n.d (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fredericks, Carleton (notes from radio show?)---re: nutrition (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Fredericks, Carleton---re: nutrition (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Psychotherapy course (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Various lectures, 1918, 1939, 1941-42, 1948, n.d (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Young, Arthur---seminar, March 1967 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Series 9 - Collected Writings/Publications
  - Acheson, Dean. “The Arrogance of International Lawyers” (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong, Herbert W. “Does God Exist?” (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong, O.K. Speech re: General MacArthur (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Author unknown. “Bovril, or Britannia Waves the Rules”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Author unknown. “Jacob Riis and His Dog”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Black, Hugo. “The Majesty of the Law” (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Bourke, Sharon. “Prison and the Painter”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Brennan, James H. “A Dramatic Address on Adam Arrived” (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Buckley, William. “Death of a Teacher: Frank Chodorow, RIP, 1887-1966”, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Cameron, K. “Memorable Teachers”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Cavander, Kenneth. “Classical Revival”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Clampett, Amy. Poetry, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Coles, Robert. “The End of the Affair”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Core, John. “Love and Women in Ovid’s Metamorphoses, Bks. 1-11” (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Costa, Robert. “The Necessity of Suffering” (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Crosby, John. Various, 1960-62 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Darrach, H.B., Jr. “The Story of the Brave Tadpole” (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Deal, J.A. “The Hillbilly or American Mountaineer” (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Devany, Edward H. “Toward the River of Return” (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - DeVoto, Bernard. “For the Wayward and Beguiled” (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Dickson, Harris. “Contraband”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Dodd, Thomas J. “The Freedom Academy Bill: The Free World’s Greatest Need” (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Edwards. Harry Stillwell. “Ereas Africanus” (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Erwin, John. “As for Ninevah: A Story Outline” (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Gardner, John. “The Ark”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Gribben, Robert E. “A Letter from Aunt Josephine” (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Hightower, Nathan. Untitled, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Hodge, Carleton T. 1956 review of T.W.Thacker’s The Relationship of Semitic and Egyptian Verb Systems (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Howard, Thomas. “The Pilgrimage of an Evangelical Catholic” (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Hu Shih. “China in Stalin’s Grand Strategy” (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Hudson, Joseph B., Jr. “Banks, Politics, Hard Circles and Paint,.. .” (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Ingram, Bowen. “Milbry”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Kahn, Otto H. “The Value of Art to the People” (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Kern, Nathaniel. Newspaper article (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Kesler, Andrew. “Pieta”, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Kinnear, James E. “Beyond Dispute: Survival of Death an Established Fact”, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood. “If You Don’t Mind My Saying So.. .” (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - McCandless, Hugh. “Must This City Lose Three Hospitals?” (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - McCormick, Col. Robert R. Various (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - McDowell, David. “The Setting Forth”, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Munsey, Frank A. Address to the American Bankers’ Association, NYC, Oct. 4, 1922: “America Is Worth Saving” (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Murrow, Edward R. News Broadcast (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Opitz, Ed. Various, 1972, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Percy, Walker. “Uncle Will and His South” (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Reading, Edna. “Travel Notes” (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Henry Morton. “Private Virtue, Public Good” (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, Logan G. “An American Lawyer in Leningrad” (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Santee, Dr. Frederick L. Latin exercises, etc., n.d, 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Scott, James Brown. “The Era of Discoveries” (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Shaw, Albert. “Ideals for the New Florida” (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Stroop, John. Various, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Temple, Robert. Various, n.d., 1955-56, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Thompson, Dorothy. Various, 1955-57 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Various authors. Miscellaneous poetry, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Verrone, Rosalia. Various poems, articles, c, 1974-72 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Yeats, John Butler. “Letters” (typescript) and review of biography (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Yoeli, Meir. Various, n.d., 1966-67, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Publications
    - Anthropological Linguistics, 1964-65 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Century Magazine, Dec. 1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Christian Economics, 1954,1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Record, 1940-41 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - The Exchange (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Fledgling, Spring (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The Freeman: Ideas on Liberty, 1960-61 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - G.K.’s Weekly, August 1, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Guideposts (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - The Italian Scene, 1954-57 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - The Landmark, Dec. 1937 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - National Review Newsletter (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - The Southwesterner Faculty Forum, Jan. 1964 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Stars and Stripes (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - The Waverly Times, 1962-65 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Series 10 - Subject Files
  - Aging (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Animals and animal rights (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Art (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Astronomy (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Atomic/nuclear weapons, energy (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Baha’i (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Book/manuscript catalogs; publishers’ brochures (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Book reviews (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Boorstin, Daniel (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Buckley, William F. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Buddhism (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Calligraphy (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Carter, Jimmy (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Cartoons (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Christian Amendment Movement (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Churchill, Winston (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Communism (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Crime (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Crime (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Drinking/prohibition (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Orthodoxy (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Economics (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Education (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Education (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Education (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Education---The Francis W. Parker School (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Education (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Evans, Walker (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Affairs (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Freemasons (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Great Britain (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Greenwich Village (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Harding, Warren G. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Harriman, Averell (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Health and nutrition (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Health and nutrition (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - History (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - History (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Human interest (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Islam (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Jarrell, Randall (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Judaism (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Korea (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Kurdian, Harry (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Labor (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Language and literature (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Lee, Robert E. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Lifeline Radio (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Lytle, Andrew (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - McCrady, Edward (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - McDowell, David (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - McLuhan, Marshall (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Mencken, H.L. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Metaphysics and psychic phenomena (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Metaphysics and psychic phenomena (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Metaphysics and psychic phenomena (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Metaphysics and psychic phenomena (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Metaphysics and psychic phenomena (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Miscellany (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - National Review (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Native Americans (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - New York City (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Nixon, Richard (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pacifism (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Parrish, Maxfield (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Peas from Tutankhamen’s tomb (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - People (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Percy, Walker (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Plays/concerts (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Politics (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Poverty (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Products (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Protests (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Psychoanalysis (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Quinn, John (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Race relations (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Race relations (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Religion (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Religion (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Restaurants (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Science (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Scientology (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Selassie, Haile (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Schriver, Sargent (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Stamp collecting (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Swedenborgians (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Tate, Allen (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Travel (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - United Nations (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - University of Virginia (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Vaughn, Sarah (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Women’s rights (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - World War II (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - World War II (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Series 11 - Financial Matters
  - Father Flye’s will, 1978. 1980, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Property in Franklin County, TN1, 1959, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Burial plots at Sewanee, TN (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1975, 1980-82 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Series 12 - Materials related to Father Flye
  - Re: Father Flye---correspondence, n.d., 1974-77 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Re: Father Flye---correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Re: Father Flye---correspondence, 1980-82 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Re: Father Flye---correspondence, Edward DeVany (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1970, 1976, 1979, n.d (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Reading at St. Luke’s (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Memorabilia (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Memorabilia (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Series 13 - Photography
  - Photography exhibit correspondence, n.d., 1979-80 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Photography exhibit correspondence, re: Jimmy Carter (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photography exhibit correspondence (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Photography exhibit correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Photography exhibit correspondence, re: book project (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Conversations with Father Flye re: photography exhibit (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Conversations with Father Flye re: photography exhibit (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Conversations with Father Flye re: photography exhibit (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Conversations with Father Flye re: photography exhibit (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Conversations with Father Flye re: photography exhibit (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Catalogue (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue, drafts and galleys (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue, drafts and galleys (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Catalogue, drafts and galleys (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Photography exhibit---clippings, 1980-82 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Photography exhibit---financial records, 1980-81 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Photography exhibit---grant application information (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Photography exhibit---miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Photography exhibit---Exhibit Opening, St. Andrew’s (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Photography exhibit---publicity, 1980, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 001-006 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 007-018 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 019-029 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 030-039 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 040-049 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 050-059 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 060-069 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 070-079 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 080-089 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 090-099 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 100-109 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 110-116 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 117-131 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 132-147 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 148-161 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 162-175 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 176-189 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 190-204 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 205-215 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 216-225 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 226-235 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 236-246 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 247-258 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 259-269 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 270-279 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 280-290 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 291-302 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 303-314 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 315-325 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 326-336 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 337-347 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 348-358 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 359-367 (Box 44, Folder 8)